yeah
who are you Angemon kendrick
lamar welcome to austin texas
appreciate you
Kendrick Lamar Thank You tech
nine right
Technine thank you what did he
do exactly help hook you up with
dr dre - all while we say how
the technology with that to
drink
well then you go to do some
concert there with a tec-9 and
Ray suddenly came to down there
oh and as the thing as a rock
limp as I go
yeah I tell the story so it's
true okay great yeah yeah it's
kinda weird uh we did the show
I don't know always at Danny's
always eating and we got a
strange car to my do a leaf fall
and hills dr e
I don't know just imagine he
called the phone and that was it
and history since then that's
crazy you know that though
Thank You tech nine thank you
take 90 k now kendrick lamar
when working with dr. dre
did he tell you anything about
his early career at all
yeah definitely what did he say
how to record was made
yeah it's early personal musical
career yeah he talking about
that
just get a momentous it was
early personal record career
yeah yeah well I have some more
for you right now candles that I
have right here
some world class Wrecking Crew
for you
yeah what they say about the
good old world class Wrecking
Crew is to start of this
motherfucking legacy head that
has passed the what he said
about this is classic matter of
fact a couple world class and
yes that's given another world
class Wrecking Crew world class
wreckin Cru
I'm surprised he could got from
dr. grace record collection
doesn't have these hanging
around there no he got he got a
dungeon that he keeps all of his
good good work like this
he doesn't like you wanted
attention at all I'm not
nobody's allowed there
kendrick lamar what's the
biggest change you ever saw
really was it on your cousin
from the south
Oh
the biggest fan ever so how's it
going yeah it was the first big
chain saw
yeah cousin family big daddy got
another gift for you
Kendrick Lamar have a right here
the big daddy
hey big daddy king what do you
tell if your big daddy kane east
coast
he's coast is one of my pops
favorite artists trailer to them
saying my pop's in chicago
he actually knows crazy when I
was coming home
you know they say when I was in
the car seat coming from the
hospital my pops is playing this
really loud
my moms like turn that shit down
here like no let him hear this
is the music is good music
big daddy kane and your mom was
one of 13 siblings
that's good stuff definitely a
big family is real big family
said quote you got like 15
stories like average Joe you got
like 15 stories
good stuff yeah you tell us one
of those who got 15 15
let's go to 13 hmm
walking from home Polly's pull
up on the side of a you look
like so and so I'm not so so you
are so get in the car let's take
this ride
get out the car you're not so on
so we don't need you anymore
that's one of the stories
compton california compton
california for you that might
make you kind of hungry but
Louisiana chicken
that's the Louisiana chickie
that's neighborhood year that's
not my favorite yeah like
bulletproof glass
yeah yeah
what do you order there i
ordered the number three is a
three piece with the fries and
lemonade
Carol Marcus also tabs and write
a to the rite aid definitely
grew up in terms and right to do
a really good research though
this is this occasion yeah tabs
the right age I get the chili
cheese fries
what about the rite aid right as
you get a bunch of milk for my
little brother's stuff like that
that
compton compilation or you get
this wrong
the compton compilation is from
about 19 but that but NWA time
have you ever seen this before I
know if you just can't MCA and
I've never seen this before i
even notice existed
we have to do you know what are
you cooking you see cmca for
sure and the white guy is well
from comptons most wanted to
return the record over right
here
what do we have underneath come
to the most wanted that's right
Rosie and the white guy
the white guy who was that the
white guy from Compton most
wanted I never knew it was a
white guy in contents most
wanted is crazy
underneath will need else we
have in a room could just
introduce them again from it
from the left here early this
moved his alley
chera a May Day free sound way
have so all here in austin texas
with kendrick lamar know about
this way either
you know this is click in my
head is that some of them
possibly
while this right here is Todd ET
who is like the first general
time t tiro a next best way to
tell you see my passport me up
on game
matter of fact my uncle tony RP
diagnose and then we can tell
people talking to use one of the
first guy first
this is one of the first you
know i will say artist and
really put it down for company
TT then you heard about in wa
but this is one of his legendary
right here take that gangsta
boogie get your real homework
sneaky Fox no but that's all I
know yeah a real nasty song my
moms and another Compton record
huh
yeah what is this the Katy
you've got some OG zone you join
my really be doing your research
bro
we're gonna come are we going to
do that represented content
Katie this is my pops would
enjoy that you shown this to me
right here King deep field and
agony bag up let's see what us
who can appreciate this rehab so
the of seeing the master of the
westside connection
come on stop see a lot of people
you know it's crazy about Josie
is you know he been doing this
before you heard the whistle
obviously you know westside
connection but still legendary
as well thanks so much for this
knowledge of Compton records its
amazin amie more knowledge did
not even you know I never knew I
never know about this right here
I never seen this
the compton compilation the
compton compilation what year is
this
I think it's about 88 yeah i'm
born 87 MC
so this 1989 actually so what
happened was in wa cages
overshadow this
so this is one of the records
where if I didn't blow but
somebody else that was doing it
blue at the me they were
shadowing me and they'll be out
and that's what happened this
and Kendrick you talk about
Compton records if i go to
Compton
I understand i got this little
handbill here there's actually
la Compton hood tours have you
seen this
I see this was this check this
out look what it says right
there la's hottest sightseeing
tour was what they put in back
of a bandwagon a
a wagon summit drive you around
yeah - all the sites like check
on the back here
I get out of here are you
serious la book tours get your
ass shot one around people you
know it's gonna be we're headed
well I hope you made this up and
i'll be general plan on getting
this is real
yea raikou any very rivalry .
please explain what's going on
please introduce who you have
right here again this is right
here is jrock we're here
projects Nixon garden project oh
I guess this is a place that we
want to see when they come to LA
and you know this dude you know
is on the forefront for ok
he happy so you meet him in the
flesh right now if you did you
know you're in this hood toward
all 90 should about the right
and do it is crazy
apparently the games dad is
involved with us he does some of
the tour's I don't know nothing
about it
I what are some of the sites if
somebody wants to check them out
what would they be visiting it
says childhood homes movies what
would they be checking out
oh man I don't know what they're
talking about trying to go to
these parts right here
my last hours on there yet I see
thee talks that they got what
they got was on you they got
what's on there
I'm quite sure they'd probably
say to accomplish want me
everything else around the edges
bullet holes let you want to see
that you had here huh
you have to ask jay rock for a
second leaving from Canada are
you familiar with the other g
rock from the trailer park boys
you know that rapper - j-rok the
trailer park boys
I never heard him canadian TV
series is a white guy chi Rock
Nine the world i'm going to
check up on
maybe when we take you on a hood
to her halifax you can check
that out
car and winding up here with
kendrick lamar Kendrick food 4
less food for less
Oh bless is you know what you
want to win over there you got
to you talked about Louisiana
you got for last is the areas
where grew up it you know and I
my stereo
we left my cereal well Fruity
Pebbles that's my favorite
cereal as you get off my food
apart from here sometime we
could afford to buy it so i had
to take some of that fruity
pebbles and eat it because it
was good guy called cannon day
your that
that's explain
it's crazy there's a cannon wow
that's crazy
can I just want to do the star
travel with what do Antonio
yeah wow that's a great a
seventh grade
how's he doing out
he's killing right now he's
doing this thing right now you
want to come up
that's crazy though Kendrick
Lamar
you also have the song i want to
be a I want to be a was that
gates our bill gates I want to
be like Bill Gates that's not it
was wondering is it bill gates
you want to be like and you know
what you're in for if you want
to be like Bill Gates see what
song was that what I don't know
: I think I was a metaphor for
saying i want to just have a lot
of fucking money and not be
stuck in all that i do know if
knows what I really want to be
like but what I mean for Bill
Gates had bono from u2 sleepover
at his house
if you have a sleepover with you
- what do you think about that
I'm good on that fit that bill
gates can also jump over a chair
so you'll be in for that are you
can you jump over a chair
I'll have him with a bit of his
rap a little bit do dogs of war
it's anything else you want to
add to the people out there at
all
Schoolboy Q ab-soul Jay Wright
te has the contradictions follow
me home
absolutely join on the way
that's going to talk about TD
that's always about you know me
is not about just one person
just about the whole movie you
take that and it's about this
city right here
mmm city of compton that day
well thanks much kendrick lamar
keep on rockin in the free world
canada talking about canon
thanks very much can you come on
your camera tomorrow I got to
know about it
keep on rockin in the free world
and do do doot do do doot
and that's normal