yeah
I
who are you future future
welcome to South by Southwest in
Austin Texas
I appreciate you for having me
my future right off the bat I
have a gift for you
I kool Moe Dee LP his throat
this is important to the future
kool Moe Dee Mary spirit you
know Sarah spray kool Moe Dee OG
legend you first get into kool
Moe Dee Brown I was on my own
my uncle's i used to listen to
the commodity future I want to
ask you about some o.g here out
of Atlanta
what can you tell the people
about these OG rap stars out of
Atlanta kilo organized base is
growing inside of my clothes and
label kilo also king j im7 any
family here uh key lime leaves
rear be to mount up . you know
means like one of the Kings in a
letter
still to this day bring kilo man
is classic Sammy Sam -
just sent myself for sure you
know I mean sem ceremony is a
living legend Lee
everyone loves a man sent
everyone we have MC shiid as
well
old-school atlanta for FCC ID -
they're always good and really
easy to do that made a loner
the Hardy Boys the whore boys
yeah man it was just like
represent the streets out of
alana back then you know it's
and these underground do that
management so much the culture
over Lana music scene
what an album cover - for a hard
place ii and horrible as I got
the name for and cool breezy
boyz great his hits is was great
as legend each . biggest star
you know I'm saying cool breeze
is his charisma his choice of
words
his wordplay was my authentic
and original universe and she's
like watch what I'm looking
he made artists out cool breeze
came over that he's the guy who
invented the term any doesn't
permit him and his family right
here
now you are future yes you do
you know of any other futures
that are out there at all future
I don't know any other features
besides our future group there
was another future it was out
there started in 2003 it was
this gentleman right here
mr. flat
top from Nashville Tennessee
originally was called future
then he changed his name to mr.
flat top and that was called a
huge huge some kids they come in
future future
so he actually was called future
in 2003 but he had to change the
changes name i guess because you
got so big
where I never heard of him who
knows it's too flat top and now
he's called future and he told
me he got quite a few emails
that were addressed to you like
managers and stuff we're looking
for you because they thought he
was you hear me shout out to mr.
flat tire you know this on my
way
future have another gift for you
and it is right here the 69 Boyz
what you think it's in our board
you think the Christmas song
everybody that's there come on
to this day another person is
crazy
I may have a long time ago he
used to come he came to the
dungeon I used to work with Rico
long time ago back in the day
you know me so I don't permit
number for mr. fab are you down
with mr. fab from the yay area
at all mr. Fairwick could do
every time I see my wish a look
from been trying to begin
he's amazing isn't he he's been
working on the grind for years
or four years we have members to
forget major look
you also down with too short to
you love the two short right man
to short his arm his brother you
know I'm saying his brother
may I was always right with his
brother back in the letter when
he lived under something to show
his brother we get along and too
short you may need 200g you know
I mean those are some of the
first round I was saying when I
was gonna have any favorite food
in Atlanta future I guess what
I'm wondering you know bisbee
has always been a classic
Spiderman just shopping to go to
eat a made any or any other wing
spot as you know is and the
wings and we have to cook them
extra crispy and what you have
it the busy bee
probably some bait black eye
peas
I used to go meet love to Z me
lo tuesdays and black eyed peas
some strings or something like
that
good vegetables are not a bread
got a good Cornbury got had a
good home brew you like
cheesecake at all
I love cheesecake cheesecake at
night I'm really tonight she's
going to do man
type it up for you go to sleep
its flavor of cheesecake you
like future is the regular one
original what does that taste
like just full-on cheese just
like cheese
but sensation
this is what are you looking for
exactly this sensation
speaking of food and stuff I
have another gift here for you
Popeye spinach reprimand is the
fray regard to all the time we
regard to the apartment so I
thought there's a pop I record
for you
that may be hidden sample and
put out on what your LPS coming
up
yeah yeah over not getting the
samples of operating properly
nose in it as our favor
future why should people care
about future why should they
care because i am the future
you're all right well thanks so
much future
keep on rockin in the free world
and do do doot do do doot
HD is posing with alternative
man kings
yeah